FROM ME TO YOU 2ND SEASON
Huh?
Where's Sawako?
Oh, she left a while ago to head off
to her school festival's after-party.
Is that so?
It's strange... Our little girl
sure does go out a lot these days...
Well, you know if she gets a
boyfriend, it is only going to get worse,
honey.
Yeah, you're right. Because once she finds
someone to marry she not going to be here
at all.
I think you might be getting a
little ahead of yourself, dear.
So what do you think,
Yano-chin? Did she get there before him?
Who knows? I bet she beat him! I mean,
they did plan to meet up so they could
walk to the party together, after all.
Am I late?
Not really.
I wonder if that's actually
what's happening right now!
- Wish I was there to tease 'em!
- What if neither of them shows up?
Ooo, I'd punch Kazehaya so hard!
I thought I was sneaking a peek at
him, but I was caught red-handed!
What's with that
reaction?! It's kinda hurtful...
I... I'm so sorry!
It's just... I'm nervous.
Yeah, I'm nervous, too.
It makes me blush.
We're the same.
I like you!
They're the same, right?
Kazehaya I want your everything...
This is like a dream!
Sa~wa~ko!
- They were just holding hands there!
- Seriously? But I thought
they were holding each other?
- Nah, it was only the hands!
- You sure?
- What?! Wait, that really happened?!
- I wish I could have seen that! Wow!
The distance was more like this...
- K-Kazehaya!
Oh, hey, Kazehaya! Since not everyone was
there, I decided to put on a reenactment
for 'em!
That's right! There was also
that thing that happened yesterday--
Hey, Joe... Do you mind if
I punch you real quick?
Wait, are you saying
what I think you're saying?!
Whoa, no way! Is it true,
Kazehaya? Do you actually like Sadako?
- What do they mean by you're "the same"?
- Does "Like a dream" mean a
nightmare? Or a good dream?
- I'm pretty sure they walked in together!
- Are you two are gonna start going out?
Oh no... Why is this happening?
Where do I even begin? Well, I...
To answer that last question...
Yeah.
Wait a sec... For real?!
- That wasn't a joke, right?
- How'd you snag Kazehaya,
- Sadako? What's your secret?
- Was it Sorcery?
No, stop!
It's me... who is head over heels for her.
It's alright! This is what
we've all been waiting for...
You understand that... don't you?
I...I feel the same.
You made me sweat for a
second there! I'm so relieved!
- It actually looks serious!
- We don't just look serious, we--
- Amazing!
Sadako, you're incredible!
Dating the Kazehaya?
I always knew that
Sadako was the real deal!
Bless me!
Me too!
- Please grant me a significant other, too.
It's not like that!
Well, this sure started
something weird, didn't it?
I guess it's okay since
they all look pretty happy.
- I can't answer prayers!
- Congrats on taking 6th place in
- the school festival, Class 2-D!
- Cheers!
Is this real?
...I can't believe it.
No...
I want to believe.
- Sa wako!
It's okay...
I'm...
I'm not a burden.
Ugh, dammit!
My top-grade sushi!
- Seriously? That's so cute!
- Wait a sec...
Jeez, it's just, Miura.
Didn't expect to see you.
- Isn't that Pin?
- I see you're with girls from another
class. It's a little late to be out here
flirting on the beach, isn't it?
What're the odds?
Shouldn't you be at that
after-party or something?
Normally, I would've tried to go, but
I got a better invite to come out here.
What about you, Mr. Arai? Don't tell me
you came to a place like this to drink
- alone!
- Oh no, how depressing...
Quiet, you!
- Hey, that's our class!
- What the...
They're... in the honeymoon phase...
Mr. "My-Feelings-Finally-Reached".
Oh, Sadako! Hey...
I'm glad to see everything
worked out! What a relief!
Thank you so much, Master...
- Oh! And Kazehaya... Come here for a sec.
- Huh? Let's have a little chat, shall we?
- What do you even want?
- It won't take long!
What's with those two?
- Have they always been that close?
- Hey, Kuronuma. Shh... over here.
Don't make her cry anymore.
It's not doing her any good.
Remember? That day when Sadako was
crying in the schoolyard... Know why?
She was really upset because she
thought there was someone else that you
- liked already.
- What? Why?
Uh, because someone told her?
Who did?
Oh, that would be me!
- So then it was your fault after all!
- Ya got me!
Also... ...it's not Sadako, it's Sawako!
Yeah? You sure?
So I can call her Sawako, then?
Sadako's fine.
I use it as a term of endearment.
About yesterday... Did you...
...tell him everything?
- Yester... Oh! That's right!
- Shh! You're being too loud!
- Pin!
- Hey, Shota, come over here for a sec.
- What do you want?
- So, you two are going out?
Y-Yeah.
Oh really? You sure you're not the
only one who thinks that's the case?
Huh? -Did you make sure to properly say
"Please go out with me" loud and clear for
- her?
- No... but I know she--
You better think again! Does she look
like someone who would fully understand
something so indirect?
Go on, ask her right now!
He's right. The way I asked
her earlier isn't enough.
Kuronuma.
Yes?
Will you please marry me?!
Ma...
...rry?!
Juuuust kidding.
- Go home! You're so annoying!
- Oh? So that's how you're gonna treat
- the person who got you this far? Come on...
- Puh...
Puh?
Please give me time to consider.
Kuronuma, I...!
Huh?
I need a little more
time to think about it
Wait, you've got it all wrong!
That's not good. Are you sure you
don't want to chase after her to expla--
Do you realize what you did?! Huh?!
You think you're funny or something?!
In the worse case, I guess,
she'll say "yes" to the proposal.
Considering it seems like she doesn't
really get jokes. So, If she took it
seriously and then you told her it was a
lie, she'd probably be hurt... it might even
make her depressed!
You're in a real pickle! Guess it doesn't
matter if you're dating or not now... So if
this ends up going south... It's all over!
Well, good luck, Shota!
Hello? Oh, hi Dad.
Uh-huh, I'm okay.
Mm, I'll try not to be
home too late tonight.
Yeah. Oh, and... if I...
A-Actually, never mind!
Hm? What is it? Tell me.
If I ever got married to
someone in the future...
...how would you feel?
Uh, on second thought,
forget I said anything!
Huh? Darling, is something the matter?
Kuronuma.
Kazehaya...
Listen...
I think you've... got it wrong. Uh...
um... a-about the marriage thing.
K-Kazehaya...
Are you trying to say that the mention of
marriage earlier was a misunderstanding?
Yeah. Punch me if you want.
No! That's not necessary at all! I
mean... I doubt anyone would have taken that
seriously, let alone me.
And it was obvious Mr. Arai was
the one who actually said it.
Whaa...?
Uh-huh.
OM dramatic relievedshocked reax
PLEASE LET ME IMAGINE IT
I... I wanna curl up and die.
Sorry... It's my fault...
I caused some confusion.
You see... all I wanted was to picture it.
Then I quickly realized that it was
something I could picture by using my
imagination.
Because of that... I think I've become a
little greedy when it comes to those kinds
of things.
I should have asked
properly. You deserve that.
I want to do this right...
...because I know if I don't,
... we can't move forward.
So please, will you go out with me?
I promise...
...I'll always care for you.
Always...?
Always?
Yes!
I... I have something really important
that I'd like to tell you too, Kazehaya.
Y-Yeah?
- Please don't hate me for it.
- I couldn't... say whatever you need to.
Well I...
I can't look at you anymore... without
having some kind of ulterior motive in
- mind!
- Kuronuma... how could I hate
you for something like that?!
Well, aren't they adorable. We
didn't have anything to worry about.
But man, I'm jealous!
Careful. Your real
feelings are showing, Yano-chin.
I mean, it's just because I
think they're such a great match.
Yeah.
I feel kind of bad for saying he's
the person who understood her the least.
Said that to who?
C'mon, who?
K-Kazehaya.
When?
Around when Sawako and
Kazehaya were becoming awkward...
- So it was you!
- I-I'm sorry, Yano-chin!
They turned out okay in the end,
so why don't you just let her go?
Shut your stupid mouth! Don't you have
some girls you could be flirting with?
Hey, Yano-chin!
Oh! Is Class C having
their after-party too?
Yup.
Where's Sadako? Is she
in her honeymoon phase?
Right on the mark, Chigusa.
Oooh. Nice! Sadako.
So, then...
it wasn't a dream!
It's strange... It still feels like
one even though I know it's not.
But for me to put this much effort
in before before going to bed means...
Uh... Are you done?
...It's reality.
I like you!
So please, will you go out with me?
I'm so happy.
This is real.
What the... What is this?!
Uh... They all want consultations...
- With black magic?!
- Sadako made Kazehaya hers?
From what I heard, Kazehaya's eyes
were glowing red when he asked her out!
I... like you. I like you!
- Scary!
- He must be completely under her spell!
- Oh wow! That makes so much sense!
- Incredible!
Sadako!
Huh?
Don't push! Wait your turn!
- Hey! Hold on, guys!
- Please!
- What are you all lining up for?
- Wait, really? 'Cause everyone who
visited the consultation booth ended up
getting to date their crush!
Wait seriously?
She's feared, she's
worshipped, she's a god now.
You should start charging money.
I'm... pretty sure that's fraud.
Honestly... if that's the perk from just
being around her... then we would have super
hot boyfriends already!
Yeah, pretty much! Like, come on! The
only guys around us are like total idiots!
Oh well As long as she
didn't get picked on, I'm glad.
- Looks like we had nothing to worry about.
- Can you lend me an item for protection?!
Maybe a shikigami!
Oh no... Don't tell me...
...Please tell me Kazehaya doesn't
believe that I have magical powers?
Really? You're sayin'this now?
Oh I'm too tired to bother at this point.
I told you...!
It's not like that at all!
I've liked Kuronuma for a while!
So the story's for
real? It's not made up?
- Are you even listening?
- Is it at least true that
- your eyes were glowing red?
- Oh, speak of the devil!
Good...
- Good morning.
You all hear that?
He's liked Sawako for a while now!
That's right! It was a
dream-come-true for him!
Hey! What makes you
think you know about--
Now that our class, and all the other
classes are actually together in one
location... ...why not make it clear, so
no one ever bothers you about it again?
Say loud and proud,
what Sawako is to you!
Poke, poke, poke, poke,
poke, poke, poke, poke.
My girlfriend!
I'm his girlfriend?!
Ooh! Finally, the naked truth!
Hearing him use that word
makes everything seem so real!
Look, I... I'm just
overwhelmed by my dream coming true.
Please leave us alone.
If you were to sum this
up, it'd be like this, right?
Yes! You hit the nail on the head!
Alright! Now's the time! Be sure to
spread the word wherever you're able!
Didn't I just say to back off?!
Whoa. Are they finally acting
like a normal, lovey- dovey couple?
They were like this at the
after party, especially Kazehaya.
You know... now that I'm getting a good look
at them, I don't know how I didn't notice
this was even possible...
...since they look so great together.
- You think so?
- Man... They really are perfect.
Oh yeah, that's right...
Kurumi got her heart broken...
...and it was Sadako who won the guy in
the end. Who would have guessed it?
My new memories... have only just begun.
Next time: "Important Person"